questionList = {
	1: {
		"question": "If you at a Coney Dog after watching a Lions NFL game in the Great Lakes state, what state are you visiting?",
		"answers":["Michigan","Wisconsin","Ohio"]
	},
	2: {
		"question":"Assemble! What Walt Disney film was the highest grossing movie of twenty nineteen?",
		"answers":["Avengers: Endgame","Captain Marvel","Aquaman"]
	},
	3: {
		"question":"Christopher Lee, Benedict Cumberbatch, and Robert Downey Junior have all portrayed what famous literary detective on the big screen?",
		"answers":["Sherlock Holmes","Dick Tracy","Batman"]
	},
	4: {
		"question":"The Big Bran Hypothetis and The Stockholm Syndrome were the first and last named episodes of what long running sitcom which ended in twenty nineteen?",
		"answers":["The Big Bang Theory","The Good Place","The Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt"]
	},
	5: {
		"question":"First said by Clara Peller in a famous nineteen eighty four commerical, what fast food chain is known for the phrase 'Where's the Beef?'",
		"answers":["Wendy's","Burger King","White Castle"]
	},
	6: {
		"question":"If you're wearing a Kangol, a Stetson, or a New Era cap, what part of your body is being covered?",
		"answers":["Head","Feet","Chest"]
	},
	7: {
		"question":"Quick! How many days total are in July, August, and September combined?",
		"answers":["92","91","93"]
	},
	8: {
		"question":"The FedEx logo is comprised of letters in purple and what other color?",
		"answers":["Orange","Green","Blue"]
	},
	9: {
		"question":"A study from the U.S. Census Bureau says, rounded up to the nearest fifteen minute interval, how many minutes per day does the average person spend commuting to work?",
		"answers":["30","45","15"]
	},
	10: {
		"question":"You'll get Eye-Eye-Eye spins if you buzz in and tell me what number equals the Roman Numeral Ex-Ex-Vee-Eye-Eye?",
		"answers":["27","32","23"]
	}
}